我从未爱得如此彻底
I never love nobody fully
爱得小心翼翼
Always one foot on the ground
怕受到伤害
And by protecting my heart truly
我迷失在这样的声音里
I got lost in the sounds
只听得到
I hear in my mind
你的声音
All of these voices
只听得到你的话语
I hear in my mind all of these words
只听得到这首歌
I hear in my mind all of this music
它使我心碎
It breaks my heart
如果没有遇见你
Suppose I never ever met you
如果我们没有相爱
Suppose we never fell in love
如果我没让你如此甜蜜温柔的亲吻我
Suppose I never ever let you kiss me so sweet and so soft
如果我们从未遇见
Suppose I never ever saw you
如果我们没有通电
Suppose we never ever called
如果我一直唱着这样的歌打破我的宁静
Suppose I kept on singing love songs just to break my own fall
打破我的宁静
Just to break my fall
To break my fall
打破我的宁静
朋友们都说我会好起来
All my friends say that of course its gonna get better
会好起来
Gonna get better
朋友们都说我会好起来
All my friends say that of course its gonna get better
会好起来
Gonna get better
好起来好起来好起来好起来
Better better better better
好起来
Better
我从未爱得如此彻底
I never love nobody fully
爱得小心翼翼
Always one foot on the ground
怕受到伤害
And by protecting by heart truly
我迷失在
I got lost
这样的声音中
In the sounds
只听得到
I hear in my mind
你的声音
All of these voices
只听得到你的话语
I hear in my mind all of these words
只听得到
I hear in my mind
这首歌
All of this music
它使我心碎
It breaks my heart